There are many monsters threatening humans
我等居住的廣大世界
in the vast world where we live.
有許多怪物 威脅著人類
Many adventurers and heroes
挺身而出的是 眾多的冒險家
stepped forward bravely.
以及勇者們
They face many dangerous challenges today
他們為了保護人們 保護世界
to protect the people and the world.
今天也面對許多危險的挑戰
And I, Alvin, is one of them.
而我埃爾文 就是其中一位
Forming a party with the healer Carla,
與僧侶卡菈組隊
let's continue the adventure today.
今天也持續冒險旅程
DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER
(這個僧侶有夠煩)
THE TITLE ALVIN AND Carla CHALLENGED A DUNGEON FOR THE FIRST TIME.
(此次的標題) (埃爾文和卡菈初次挑戰迷宮)
THE DUNGEON IS DESIGNED FOR BEGINNERS. EVEN ALVIN SHOULD BE ABLE TO MAKE IT THROUGH.
(該迷宮設計成適合新手的模式) (應該連埃爾文都能攻略吧)
BUT HE WAS CALLED A VETERAN ROOKIE WASN'T FOR NO REASON.
(但他之所以會被稱為新人老手) (果然不是叫假的)
"THE TRAP CAVE HERE" Mr. Alvin, where are we going today?
(在此平凡出現的陷阱洞穴) 埃爾文先生 今天要去哪
"APPEARED ENDLESSLY LIKE STUNTS (?)." A dungeon.
(就像特技表演(?)般的層出不窮) 迷宮
"THE NAME OF THIS MUSHROOM MONSTER IS Altargaia." Are you kidding me?
(這隻蘑菇怪的名字是奧爾特蓋亞) 開玩笑嗎
"THERE MAY BE NO CHANCE TO CALL IT,BUT REMEMBER THE NAME." I'm serious.
(雖然應該沒機會叫 但還是記一下名字) 我是認真的
"APART FROM PAUSING ANIMATION, PLEASE ALSO GO TO" You think it's too hard for me, don't you?
(除了暫停動畫之外 還有上官網確認這個方式) 妳覺得對我來說太難了是吧
"THE OFFICIAL WEBSITE TO CONFIRM. THAT'S EPISODE FOUR." No, but everyone probably thinks so.
(還請多加利用 在此告知的第四話) 我沒這麼覺得 但大家可能這麼想
Don't worry. The dungeon we're going to is suitable for beginners.
放心吧 我要去的迷宮 是適合新手的迷宮
So it's a dungeon for you, Mr. Alvin.
就是埃爾文先生專用的迷宮
Am I the master of the dungeon?
我是迷宮的主人嗎
I got it.
我知道了
It's your house, right?
是你家對吧
I said, we're going to "a dungeon."
我說了是去"迷宮"
I found it. There's a building ahead.
找到了 前方有建築物
It should be there.
應該就在那
This is my first dungeon adventure.
這是我首次的迷宮冒險了
It's getting a little nervous.
有點緊張吧
All right. Let's go!
好 走吧
WELCOME TO DUNGEON FOR ABSOLUTE BEGINNERS
(歡迎來到超新手取向迷宮)
DON'T WORRY IT'S SAFE
(安心 安全)
Your house is so unique.
你家好有特色喔
Is it a designer's house?
是設計師之家嗎
It's not my house.
這不是我家
If it were my house, I'd find the designer and his descendants even after I died.
若真是我家 我死也要找設計師 和他的後代子孫作祟
What should we do now?
現在該怎麼辦呢
The dungeon is very different from what I thought.
雖然跟想像中的迷宮差異很大
But let's go in first...
但總之先進去…
Hold up.
慢著
Are you a monster?
是魔物嗎
Warrior, put your sword down.
這位戰士 放下劍
I have no intention to fight with you.
我無與你戰鬥之意
What?
什麼
Even if you don't have it, we do.
就算你沒有 但我們有
Let's fight.
要打了喔
Clergy shouldn't look for fights.
聖職人員別愛好爭鬥啊
Do you want to enter the dungeon?
你們想進迷宮嗎
If we do, so what? Do you want to stop us?
那又怎樣 想阻止我們嗎
I just said I have no intention to fight with you.
方才我已說過 無戰鬥之意
-Look. It just said that. -But it's a dungeon for absolute beginners.
-你看 人家剛才都說了 -但這裡是新人取向迷宮
-You're the one who wants to fight most. -Is it really suitable for you to enter?
-妳才是最想打的人吧 -真的適合你們進入嗎
Hey, listen to me!
喂 聽我說
-Huh? -What's that?
-咦 -要聽什麼
So you weren't listening to me.
你們果然沒在聽
I hardly act so seriously…
我難得表現的如此嚴肅耶…
Do you mean
意思是說
only beginners can enter this dungeon?
這座迷宮只有新人才能進入嗎
Someone was listening to me. That's great.
有人聽我的話 真是太好了
About that, Mr. Alvin has a one-year beginner pass.
關於這點 埃爾文先生 擁有新手一年通行證
I don't, okay?
沒有好嗎
It's okay. I just have to look into you.
算了 只要調查一下就知道
Here I go.
開始囉
This…
這是…
One, one, one hundred!
一 一 一百
Beginner Level 100!
新手等級 一百
What a pity.
超慘
I knew this would happen.
我就知道會這樣
Useless Level 100.
沒用等級100
I understand.
我懂
I can't tell what you understand.
我聽不出妳懂什麼
It also means to stay true to yourself…
這也有不要忘記初衷之意…
PUFF
(噗)
Your comfort makes me feel even worse.
你的安慰讓我更難過
All right. Please come in.
好的請進
What's with that music?
什麼音樂
First dungeon adventure.
首次迷宮冒險
We're going to challenge it, right?
開始攻略了對吧
Yes.
是啊
Be careful on the way.
攻略路上小心喔
Okay. Thank you.
好的 謝謝
I'm tired.
累了
It's tiring just by entering.
光是入口就覺得好疲累
But this is a dungeon. I can't be like this.
這裡不過是座迷宮 不行這樣
Pull myself together.
重新打起精神
There may be traps inside.
裡面不知道有什麼陷阱
Listen, you two.
你們聽好了
It's for beginners, but it's still a dungeon.
雖然這是新手取向 但仍是迷宮
Be careful of your surroundings…
一定要小心周遭…
There it is.
出現了
Mr. Alvin's useless Level 100 skill.
埃爾文先生的沒用等級100技能
Mr. Alvin, are you all right?
埃爾文先生 你還好嗎
There's a blanket at the bottom.
底下有毛毯
A ladder on the wall.
牆上有梯子
It's a trap of a beginner dungeon indeed.
不愧是新手取向迷宮裡的陷阱
Hurry up and come up.
快點上來吧
You're not injured, after all.
反正你又沒受傷
He feels so down.
他很沮喪耶
Really. I'll go and encourage him.
真是的 我去鼓勵他
Mr. Alvin.
埃爾文先生
Awesome. Hole-in-one.
很棒 一桿進洞
You're indeed a professional teacher of bad example.
不愧是專業的 反面教材教師
Have your brain cells for encouraging others all gone?
妳鼓勵人的腦細胞是死光了嗎
I don't like falling into a trap, either…
我也不喜歡踩中陷阱…
Okay… I know.
好… 我知道
Actually, I've prepared a magic prop against traps.
其實我準備了對抗陷阱的魔法道具
Here you go.
來 拿去
Really?
真的假的
Come on. You should've given it to me earlier…
什麼嘛 有道具就早點拿…
What is it? A normal cloth?
這是什麼 普通的布
Well, a beginner doesn't know that.
真是的 新手果然不懂嗎
Listen. If you're trapped again,
聽好了 之後若中了陷阱
Trapped…
中了陷阱…
You would feel ashamed and upset.
一定會覺得既丟臉又難過吧
So please use it to wipe your tears.
所以請拿去擦眼淚吧
It's just a normal handkerchief!
這只是普通的手帕嘛
I'm not going to cry.
我才不會哭呢
How rude.
沒禮貌
It's frequently used when cleaning.
那是打掃時很活躍的東西耶
So it's a rag.
那這就是抹布
I won't get trapped again.
只要不再中陷阱就好了吧
Let's go.
走啦
Concentrate. Pay attention to the surroundings.
集中精神 注意周遭狀況
Detect danger and avoid it as soon as possible.
盡早發覺危險並迴避
Concentrate. Pay attention to the surroundings…
集中精神 注意周遭狀況…
It's getting darker.
越來越暗了
It's dark here. Watch your step.
這裡很暗 要小心腳下喔
I know.
知道
Mr. Alvin.
埃爾文先生
Pull that lever. Maybe it can turn on the lights.
拉拉看那個手把 搞不好能點燈喔
That lever?
拉那個手把嗎
I see. That makes sense.
原來如此 有道理
It's so dark and hard to see the traps.
這麼暗 很難看到陷阱
It's a beginner dungeon indeed.
不愧是新手取向迷宮
I'm not crying.
我沒哭
Don't act tough. Come on.
別逞強 來
Don't give me the rag.
別拿抹布給我
Stop fooling around. Let's go.
別玩了 快走吧
I'm not fooling around!
我才沒玩呢
Concentrate. Pay attention to the surroundings. Detect danger and avoid it as soon as possible.
集中精神 注意周遭狀況 盡早發覺危險並迴避
Hey, Alvin.
我說埃爾文
I didn't expect you'd fall into such a boring trap.
沒想到你竟然會中這麼無聊的陷阱
To be honest, don't you think you're not fit to be an adventurer?
老實說 你是不是不適合當冒險家
NOT FIT
(不適合)
It's a misunderstanding.
你誤會了
Misunderstanding?
誤會
Mr. Alvin sacrificed himself
埃爾文先生為了不讓我們中陷阱
so that we wouldn't fall into the trap.
所以才捨生取義的
Really?
真的嗎
Of course.
當然是真的
People normally won't fall into such a simple trap.
一般人才不會中這麼簡單的陷阱呢
Right, Mr. Alvin?
埃爾文先生 對吧
You found it out.
被妳發現啦
So it's true.
果然是這樣
It's a warrior's duty to keep companions safe.
保護同伴安全 也是戰士的義務
You're amazing, Mr. Alvin.
太了不起了 埃爾文先生
Don't mention it.
別說了
You should've just told us.
直接告訴我們就好啦
Right? Why did you put yourself in danger?
對吧 幹嘛以身試險呢
Don't compliment me, then mock me again!
別把人推上天堂又踢下地獄啊
Do you like getting trapped recently?
你最近是不是喜歡上中陷阱啦
Don't say like as if getting trapped is a hobby.
別說的好像中陷阱是種興趣好嗎
Alvin, watch your step.
埃爾文 注意腳邊
Oh no, we're locked up.
糟糕 被關起來了
The wall…
牆壁…
Oh, crap. We'll be crushed if it goes on.
不好 再這樣下去 我們會被壓扁的
What should we do…
怎麼辦…
It stops as soon as I push it gently.
輕輕推就停了
Mr. Alvin.
埃爾文先生 埃爾文先生
When did you get out?
什麼時候出去的
Did you use magic?
妳使用了魔法嗎
No. There's a door within the iron fence.
不 是鐵柵欄有門喔
Look.
你看
The more flustered you're, the less you can see what's in front of you.
人越慌張 就越看不清眼前的事物
Concentrate. Pay attention to the surroundings.
集中精神 注意周遭狀況
That's great, Mr. Alvin.
太好了 埃爾文先生
You fell into every trap since the beginning.
從頭到尾 每個陷阱都中
That must be what the traps expected.
陷阱一定也這麼期望的吧
Why do you personify traps?
幹嘛把陷阱擬人化啊
Traps exist to make people fall into them.
陷阱是為了讓人中計而存在的
In this way, Mr. Alvin is an ideal adventurer.
就這個意義上來看 埃爾文先生簡直是理想的冒險家
I don't want to be such an ideal adventurer.
我才不想成為這種理想冒險家
Look over there.
你們快看
That's…
那是…
A door.
是門耶
There's no other path.
沒有其他岔路
It goes straight to the end.
一條路直直通到底
"PLEASE PRESS IF YOU NEED IT" There seems to be something like a button.
(需要的人請按) 好像有個類似按鈕的東西
It's probably a trap again.
八成又是陷阱吧
It's too obvious that it's suspicious.
明顯地太詭異了
It's most likely a trap.
十之八九是陷阱吧
That's right.
就是說啊
What should we do…
怎麼辦…
I'll leave it to you, Pro Alvin.
拜託你了 埃爾文專家
Who are you calling a pro?
誰是專家啊
As you always do.
就像平常那樣
What do I always do?
平常的哪樣啦
I'll press it as you wish.
如妳所願 我就按下去吧
ANTICIPATING
(期待)
"PLEASE PRESS IF YOU NEED IT" Concentrate. Pay attention to the surroundings.
(需要的人請按) 集中精神 注意周遭狀況
Detect danger and avoid it as soon as possible.
盡早發覺危險並迴避
All right. I'm going to press it.
好 我要按囉
Okay.
好
That must be a trap. It's dangerous.
那絕對是陷阱啦 很危險耶
But there's no other way.
可是沒有其他道路了
Well, right…
是沒錯啦…
I'm going to press it.
要按囉 要按囉
I'm doing it. I'm going to press it.
我真的要按囉 按下去囉
No matter what happens, don't panic.
不管發生什麼都別慌喔
Where will the trick come from?
機關會從哪裡來
Up? Down? Right? Left?
上面 下面 右邊 左邊
Will it come from the back… Both of you!
難道是後面… 你們兩個
The door may not open even if I press it.
就算按了 門也不一定會開
I'm still afraid that it's a trap.
我果然還是擔心是陷阱
We should be cautious...
這種時候要慎重…
Oh, right. It may be safer to press it with a sword.
對了 用劍去按 搞不好會比較安全
So I won't be the target of the trap.
這樣就不會成為陷阱的目標了
Okay. I'm going to press it.
好 我要按囉
It opened.
打開了
You broke it open!
是打破了吧
That's a terrible wink.
眨眼還是那麼難看
The result is the same.
以結果來說是相同的
Except that you destroyed things.
撇除了妳破壞物品這件事
What was that noise?
剛才的聲響是怎麼回事
It sounds like breaking the door with "Tetsuzanko."
聽起來就像是 用"鐵山靠"把門打破的聲音
What happened?
到底發生什麼事了
DOMESTIC-MADE
(國產)
The door was broken…
門真的被打破了…
What's coming?
什麼東西過來了
Suspicious person.
可疑之人
For the current situation, that's us…
以目前的情況來看 我們才是…
Could it be that you're the adventurers?
你們該不會是 冒險家
Sort of…
算是吧…
I knew it.
我就知道
All right, don't stand here. Come on in.
好了 別站在這裡說話 快進來吧
It seems to welcome us.
牠好像很歡迎我們耶
Is it a trap as well?
這也是陷阱嗎
Go in and have a look first.
先進去看看吧
Even if it's a trap, it's designed for beginners. Who would be trapped?
就算是陷阱 也是新人取向 誰會中計呢
Come on in. Help yourselves.
快進來 不用客氣
Say it if you dare.
有種就說啊
No, it's nothing.
不 沒什麼
Come on. This way.
來 這邊請
Please have a seat.
來 請坐
Have some tea.
請喝茶
Okay. Thank you.
好的 謝謝
Could it be poisonous?
難道 裡面有毒
You're drinking it?
妳竟然喝下去了
It's warm. And it tastes awful.
是溫的 而且超難喝
You're being too honest.
太老實了吧
Sorry, I'll get you a new one.
對不起 我馬上重泡一杯
"BULL SERVING DRESSING WEIGHT" The serving level is way too high!
(牛 招待 打扮 體重) 招待指數高過頭了吧
By the way, who are you…
話說回來 你到底是…
I'm the master of this dungeon.
我是這座迷宮的主人
You finally came here, foolish adventurers.
你們終於來到我這啦 愚蠢的冒險家們
Now only you're so aggressive…
你現在才這麼有氣勢也…
I advise you to get changed.
我勸你換套衣服
DOMESTIC-MADE
(國產)
Even a beginner won't fall into those simple traps.
就算是新手 也不可能中那些 簡單至極的陷阱
Huh? Did you fall into those traps?
不會吧 你該不會中陷阱了
I'm so happy.
我真是太開心了
I didn't expect an adventurer would fall into them.
竟然有冒險家中那些陷阱
Even if you're a beginner, it's too…
就算你是新手也太…
What's so funny about that?
有什麼好笑的
One of us sacrificed.
我們有人犧牲了耶
Don't say it as if someone died, okay?
不要說的好像有人死了好嗎
How… How could it be…
怎…怎麼會這樣…
The safety myth of the dungeon was finally ruined.
這座迷宮的安全神話 終於崩壞了
I'm alive.
我還活著
What… have I done?
我…做了什麼
You finally found out your sins.
你終於發現自己所犯下的罪孽
I didn't mean to kill someone.
我沒打算殺人啊
Since you're a monster, you should be aware of killing someone.
既然你是魔物 就做好殺人的覺悟啊
Everyone makes mistakes.
誰都有犯錯的時候
The most important thing is to make up for your sins.
最重要的是如何補償罪行
How to make up?
如何 補償
Stop wavering, cleric.
別動搖了 聖職人員
I got it.
我知道了
Please wait a minute.
請稍等
Yet, all I have left…
話雖如此 我只剩下…
After all, I worked very hard.
畢竟我經營得很辛苦
Just give it to me then.
既然要給 就拿來吧
A coin jewelry?
硬幣首飾
Is it a magic item?
是魔法道具嗎
No. It's a souvenir for adventurers who come to the dungeon.
不 是來迷宮的冒險家 都能拿到的紀念品
It looks like just jewelry.
乍看之下只是一枚首飾
Perhaps…
搞不好…
What is it?
怎麼了
It's just trash.
只是個垃圾
Mind your words!
看氣氛說話好嗎
Everybody, have you got drinks?
各位 都拿到飲料了嗎
Then let's celebrate Carla and her party challenging the dungeon.
那麼 慶祝卡菈一行人攻略迷宮
Cheers.
乾杯
Thank you for your hard work.
你辛苦啦
Wait a second. It's too weird.
給我等一下 太怪了吧
Why are we celebrating happily with the monster?
為何要跟魔物和樂融融地慶祝啊
And I didn't get the drink yet.
還有 我沒拿到飲料
Let me take this opportunity to talk about it.
趁這個機會讓我好好說說
How much longer are you going to follow us?
你到底要跟著我們到什麼時候
Since you're the dungeon master, show your majesty!
既然你是迷宮之主 那就有點威嚴好嗎
Let me share the salad.
我來幫大家分沙拉喔
It's not time to share the salad!
現在是分沙拉的時候嗎
Let's be frank today.
今天 我們就敞開心來說吧
Mr. Alvin, can you give me a massage?
埃爾文先生 你能幫我按摩嗎
Are you a tyrant?
妳是暴君嗎
Mr. Alvin.
埃爾文先生
What's wrong?
幹嘛
You're too excited. It's embarrassing.
你興奮過頭了 這樣很丟臉喔
I'm getting angry.
我是在生氣
And you're the excited one.
還有 興奮的人是妳吧
What's that costume? Birthday party?
妳那什麼裝扮 生日派對嗎
Your costume is weirder.
埃爾文的裝扮才奇怪呢
Warrior costume party?
戰士的裝扮派對嗎
I'm dressed as usual.
我的裝扮跟平常一樣耶
But I understand your excitement.
不過我懂你覺得興奮的心情
As an adventurer, it's my first time challenging the dungeon.
身為冒險家 這也是我首次攻略迷宮
Is it your first time too?
你也是第一次嗎
Yes.
是啊
It's not warm.
不是溫的
That makes sense.
說的也是
For her personality,
以這傢伙的性格來看
she'll be kicked out wherever she goes.
不管去哪都會被趕出來
That's why her behavior is so boastful.
所以行為才會這麼浮誇
I've been refused to join many teams
我也曾因實力不足
due to my lack of strength.
而被拒絕加入許多團隊
Excuse me. Do you want to…
請問 要不要一起…
Sorry, but your level…
抱歉 你的等級有點…
He's a veteran rookie.
是萬年新手
In other words,
也就是說
today is the day you two managed to challenge the dungeon for the first time.
今天是兩位 首次成功攻略迷宮的日子
It's a day of commemoration.
是紀念日啊
Did we manage to challenge it? I'm not sure about that.
能說攻略成功嗎 有點微妙就是了
Day of commemoration...
紀念日…
It's... our party's... day of commemoration.
是我們…隊伍的…紀念日
Why? Are you happy?
怎麼 妳很開心嗎
No. It's normal.
不 很普通啊
Am I right? Are you shy?
我說中了嗎 妳在害羞嗎
What's wrong with you? Do you want to see how the hell is?
怎樣啦 你想見識地獄嗎
What a dangerous way of being shy.
真危險的害羞方式
Since we managed to challenge it.
對我們來說 既然攻略成功了
Come on.
來
What is it?
幹嘛
Don't you know that? High five.
妳不懂嗎 擊掌啊
Companions always do so when achieving goals together.
同伴一起達成目標時 經常會這樣做
Companions always do so…
同伴經常這樣…
You liar.
你騙人
Mr. Alvin, you have no experience in forming a team with others.
埃爾文先生沒有與他人組隊的經驗
Yet, you said "companions always do so." It's too contradictory.
竟然說"同伴經常這樣做" 實在太矛盾了
It's so weird.
超怪
It's not.
才不怪呢
You real intention is…
你真正的目的是…
Use high five as an excuse to touch my body.
以擊掌為藉口 碰觸我的身體吧
All right. It doesn't matter if you don't want to do it.
好啦好啦 不想擊掌也無所謂啦
MOST OUTSTANDING AWARD
(最優秀獎)
We're companions, anyway.
我們 是同伴嘛
A little body touch is okay.
少許的身體接觸 也行啦
She's so annoying.
這傢伙真的超煩的
Okay, I got it. Come on.
好啦我知道了啦 來
There… There's no choice.
真… 真拿你沒辦法
Let's celebrate us challenging the dungeon successfully for the first time.
慶祝我們首次成功攻略迷宮
Honestly. She's obviously happy.
真是的 明明就很開心
Thank you for your hard work.
辛苦你啦
Thank you for challenging the dungeon.
謝謝你們來攻略迷宮
You did a great job.
辛苦你們了
The food was very delicious. Thank you very much.
料理非常美味 多謝款待
I had a great time.
我玩得很開心
"WELCOME TO DUNGEON FOR ABSOLUTE BEGINNERS" Good luck with your adventure.
(歡迎來到超新手取向迷宮) 祝你們冒險順利
What an interesting party.
真是有趣的團隊
All right. I have to fix the door inside.
好了 我得去修好裡面那扇門了
Until when you're going to wear that hat?
妳打算帶那頂帽子到什麼時候
Mr. Bull gave me that as a souvenir.
難得人家牛先生給我做紀念
It's rude to take it off as Mr. Bull still can see us.
在牛先生還看得到的範圍內 就拿下來 太沒禮貌了
Will it?
會嗎
Yes.
會
Oh right, Alvin.
對了 埃爾文
What's the matter?
什麼事
The button in the dungeon isn't a trap.
迷宮裡的按鈕 不是陷阱喔
It's a normal doorbell.
是普通的門鈴
I see. It's really a beginner dungeon.
是喔 不愧是新手取向的迷宮
It's getting late.
已經這麼晚啦
Hopefully, we can find a hotel before sunset.
希望能在太陽下山前找到旅館
Right, Carla?
對吧 卡菈
What... What are you talking about?
你你你你在說什麼呢
-Well, find a hotel… -Find a hotel, right? Hurry up then.
-就是 找旅館… -找旅館是吧 那就快點動身吧
Well, Miss Carla. You're a little strange.
那個 卡菈小姐 妳有點怪喔
Strange… I don't want to be said so by someone strange.
怪… 我才不想被怪的人說怪
Do you mean I'm interestingly strange?
妳的意思是我很有趣的怪嗎
Or pervertedly strange?
還是說我是變態的怪
Perverted.
變態
What?
什麼
Mr. Mushroom is gone.
香菇先生不見了
Oh, he'll catch up soon anyway.
是喔 反正他馬上就會追上來了
You're right.
說的也是
We can pay less for the accommodation fee.
這樣就不用多付一人住宿費了
What a terrible cleric.
真糟糕的聖職人員
I'm worried about your wallet, Mr. Alvin.
我是擔心埃爾文先生的錢包
Who are you calling poor?
你說誰很窮啊
WHERE AM I
(我在哪)
"NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW" Title of the next episode.
(下集預告) 下集的標題
"THIS WORLD IS FULL OF DEMONS AND MONSTERS" When Elvin and Kara
(再次認知這個世界到處都是披著人類外皮的魔物和怪物) 埃爾文和卡菈打算在旅館住宿時
"AND THE NAME OF THE HOTEL IS 'PIG GIRL'S PLACE.'" the owner who seemed nice
(而旅館的名字是"住宿少女豬") 看起來人很好的老闆
"SOME PEOPLE MAY NOT KNOW WHERE IT COMES FROM." revealed her true colors
(或許有人不知哏從哪來 總之就是部有名的作品) 因卡菈的緣故露出了真面目
"THOSE WHO KNOW WILL FEEL SO NOSTALGIC." Then the nature of an old woman
(知道的人就會覺得好懷念) 接著在路上遇到的老婆婆
"I HAVEN'T SEEN IT FOR A LONG TIME. I WANT TO SEE IT." met on the way was very unexpected.
(好久沒看了好想看喔) 其本性令人十分意外
"AND I'M IMMERSED IN THESE FEELINGS. THAT'S EPISODE FIVE." In this world,
(並沉浸在這些感慨中的第5話) 這個世界
"STAY TUNED" not all, but…
(要繼續觀看喔) 雖不能說全部 但…